# Muhamma

# **ABOUT ME**

A full-stack Python Developer working on projects related to python, Cloud (AWS, GCP). I inspire to become a Machine Learning Engineer.

Lived in Qatar for 18 years and moved to Pakistan for pursuing Software Engineering at UET TAXILA.

Keen to learn more and implement in life to solve problems using code. I have experience coding in the following tech stacks:

- Full Stack MERN (MongoDb, Express, React.js, Node.js) Development
- Python development (Scripting, Django)
- Data Science (Numpy, Pandas, scikit-learn)
- Using Firebase as a backend service for Web and App
- Using Dialogflow for creating Google Assitant agents
- SQL Database Management
- Linux/Unix

# **EDUCATION**

University of Engineering and technology, Taxila

2018 - 2022 | Bachelor's in Software Engineering

Pakistan International School Qatar

2009 - 2017 | FSc in Pre-engineering

# **EXPERIENCE**

### 2018-Present

### **Python Development**

- Working on Python projects related to Scripting and back-end
- Django Development for React.js and HTML, CSS, JS front-end.

### 2019-20

# **Developer Student Club Core Team Member**

- Technical and Non-Technical Lead (GCP and Social Media).
- Conducted workshops related to Machine Learning in Cloud and Actions on Google.

### 2017

## **Qatar University Research Intern**

- Operated state of the art machinery.
- Worked with the Head of Department of the Research Complex.
- Learned a lot of valuable skills by working along side talented chemical engineers.
- Managed other interns as a senior intern.

# CONTACT

+92 309 5688 733 muhdsaad107@gmail.com http://www.muhdsaad107.me